<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FoodAllergyScanner</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <p><b>App Description</b>: This app was designed to quickly identify if an
        item is unsafe to consume by using a barcode scanner on a device
        you will never be without. This app was not designed to identify
        whether to item is safe to consume.</p>
        <br>
        <p><b>Directions</b>: Upon opening the application, accept the disclaimer
        and enter your all of your allergies in the settings. When you come
        across a product you would like to test to see if it contains
        one of your listed allergies press the scanner button and hold
        the barcode of the product half an arms length away from the
        scanner. The camera on the phone will auto focus by itself, and
        you just need to hold it there. Once the scanner identifies the
        item, and reveals whether you may be able to consume it make sure
        to double check the ingredients list if the item says its safe.</p>
        <br>
        <p><b>Disclaimer</b>: This app is designed to be a suggestion and should
        not under any circumstances take place of actually reading labels
        and ingredients. If the app says your item may or does contain
        substances you are allergic to DO NOT CONSUME THE PRODUCT. If the
        app says the item may be safe,you MUST READ THE LABEL before using.
        If the database does not recognize the item you have,DO NOT CONSUME
        THE ITEM. In addition the database has shown to be accurate, but
        may still be have errors, so do not rely on the app in life or death
        situations.</p>
        <br>
        License info
        <br>
        <br>
        <br>
        <br>
        <br>
        <br>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="disclaimer">
        <![CDATA[

        <b>Disclaimer</b>
        <br>
        <br>
        This app is designed to be a suggestion and should
        not under any circumstances take place of actually reading labels
        and ingredients. If the app says your item may or does contain
        substances you are allergic to DO NOT CONSUME THE PRODUCT. If the
        app says the item may be safe, you MUST READ THE LABEL before using.
        If the database does not recognize the item you have, DO NOT CONSUME
        THE ITEM. The database has shown to be accurate, but
        may still have errors, so do not rely on the app in situations
        in which a persons health is in danger. By pressing continue, you are
        agreeing to use the app responsibly, and not sue the developers if something
        goes wrong.
        <br>
        <br>
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
